<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>Intisar Bin Naim</title>
        <link>https://intisarbnaim.com/</link>
        <description>Hi, I&#39;m Intisar! Welcome to my personal blog. I enjoy talking about design and development.</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><managingEditor>intisarbnaim@gmail.com (Intisar Bin Naim)</managingEditor>
            <webMaster>intisarbnaim@gmail.com (Intisar Bin Naim)</webMaster><copyright>This work is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial 4.0 International License.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2023 20:14:57 &#43;0600</lastBuildDate>
            <atom:link href="https://intisarbnaim.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
        <item>
    <title>HTML Table Generator</title>
    <link>https://intisarbnaim.com/html-table-generator/</link>
    <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2023 20:14:57 &#43;0600</pubDate>
    <author>Intisar Bin Naim</author>
    <guid>https://intisarbnaim.com/html-table-generator/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[HTML Table Generator is a WPF application that takes user input and generates HTML table code, making the process much easier.
Backstory I was working on an ebook file that I planned to read on my Kindle. The file had numerous Japanese dialogues and vocabularies that needed to be turned into an HTML table for the kindle to display properly. I also had to use HTML ruby syntax to ensure that it supported Furigana.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>Furigana Tool</title>
    <link>https://intisarbnaim.com/furigana-tool/</link>
    <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2023 20:13:57 &#43;0600</pubDate>
    <author>Intisar Bin Naim</author>
    <guid>https://intisarbnaim.com/furigana-tool/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Furigana Tool automates the process of writing HTML code for Furigana with ruby syntax. It uses a modified version of the Gem library and adds a User Interface to it.
This tool was designed to work in conjunction with the HTML Table Generator which I created for another project.
The Ruby Syntax &ldquo;A ruby annotation is a small extra text, attached to the main text to indicate the pronunciation or meaning of the corresponding characters.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>Let&#39;s Learn C# (03) — What is C#?</title>
    <link>https://intisarbnaim.com/cs-03-what-is-c-sharp/</link>
    <pubDate>Wed, 14 Sep 2022 20:13:57 &#43;0600</pubDate>
    <author>Intisar Bin Naim</author>
    <guid>https://intisarbnaim.com/cs-03-what-is-c-sharp/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[What is C#? C# is a general-purpose, multi-paradigm, type-safe programming language that runs on the .NET platform.
Although the definition is short, there are several terms that need a little discussion.
General Purpose Language Here, the term &lsquo;general purpose&rsquo; refers to the ability to do a wide range of tasks using a single language. Here&rsquo;s a list of things you can do once you&rsquo;ve learned C#:
Web Application Development: Using C#, you can easily create dynamic websites and web apps for the .]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>Let&#39;s Learn C# (02) — Why C#?</title>
    <link>https://intisarbnaim.com/cs-02-why-c-sharp/</link>
    <pubDate>Wed, 14 Sep 2022 00:09:40 &#43;0600</pubDate>
    <author>Intisar Bin Naim</author>
    <guid>https://intisarbnaim.com/cs-02-why-c-sharp/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Why learn C# when there are so many other programming languages? First of all, congratulations on choosing a popular language such as C#. Rest assured you will never regret your decision to learn the language. If you want to become a good .NET developer or work with Unity, there is no alternative to C#.
The following are other reasons why learning C# is a good idea:
1. C# code is easy to read As a developer, you will spend far more time reading code than writing it.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>Let’s Learn C# (01) — Journey Starts</title>
    <link>https://intisarbnaim.com/cs-01-journey-starts/</link>
    <pubDate>Tue, 13 Sep 2022 13:11:09 &#43;0600</pubDate>
    <author>Intisar Bin Naim</author>
    <guid>https://intisarbnaim.com/cs-01-journey-starts/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Some Words Years ago, I once tried teaching programming to one of my younger brothers. He was interested in game development with Unity, and I am also comfortable with C#, so I started with this language. While teaching, I noticed he wanted all the resources to be in Bangla, such as Bangla courses, Bangla books, etc. Not only that, he also wanted everything to be concise. What he wanted to learn should be to the point, nothing extra.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>Browse the Web More Quickly and Securely</title>
    <link>https://intisarbnaim.com/browse-web-faster/</link>
    <pubDate>Mon, 12 Sep 2022 10:09:02 &#43;0600</pubDate>
    <author>Intisar Bin Naim</author>
    <guid>https://intisarbnaim.com/browse-web-faster/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[The internet has become a part of our existence now. The fact that you are reading this article is also because of the internet. An internet connection, as well as a browser, is necessary to browse the internet. Today I&rsquo;ll talk about these browsers and show how you can use the internet more quickly and safely.
1. Selecting a Browser The first step is to select a browser. Yes, I know you are already using a browser, be it Google Chrome, Mozilla&rsquo;s Firefox, or any other browser.]]></description>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
